Finding Aid for Angela Morgan Papers 1861-1957
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Poems
  - Always Ready People (Box 29)
  - Amazons (Box 29)
  - Ambition of the Stones (Box 29)
  - Amelia Earhart (Box 29)
  - America's Westminster Abbey, 1924 (Box 29)
  - American Anthem, 1929 (Box 29)
  - Ancestry, 1922 (Box 29)
  - Angel at Your Elbow (Box 29)
  - Angel-Engineer (Box 29)
  - Angel Pillows, 1937 (Box 29)
  - Angela's Room, 1953 (Box 29)
  - Angels at the Feast, 1929 (Box 29)
  - Anguished Cry (Box 29)
  - Anne, 1935 (Box 29)
  - Announce the New Dawn (Box 29)
  - Answer, Soldiers (Box 29)
  - Answer, World (Box 29)
  - Appeal to the Unknown Soldier, 1931 (Box 29)
  - Appointed Lover (Box 29)
  - April Air, 1923 (Box 29)
  - April Evening, 1921 (Box 29)
  - April O-Clock, 1929 (Box 29)
  - April Sun (Box 29)
  - April Trees (Box 29)
  - Archaeologists (Box 29)
  - Ariadne, 1925 (Box 29)
  - Arizona Mountains (Box 29)
  - Armored Knight (Box 29)
  - Army, 1939 (Box 29)
  - Art Triumphant, 1928 (Box 29)
  - Artist (Box 29)
  - Assault on the Infinite (Box 29)
  - Assurance (Box 29)
  - At Breakfast, 1929 (Box 29)
  - At the Piano (Box 29)
  - Atom (Box 29)
  - Atomic Energy (Box 29)
  - Autumn (Box 29)
  - Autumn in the Mountains (Box 29)
  - Autumn Panoply (Box 29)
  - Autumn Song (Box 29)
  - Awakening, 1917 (Box 29)
  - Bad, 1916 (Box 29)
  - Bakery (Box 29)
  - Ballad of the Wind and the Pine, 1918 (Box 29)
  - Bargain, 1928 (Box 29)
  - Barred (Box 29)
  - Basques and Bonnets (Box 29)
  - Bathe Me, O Stars (Box 29)
  - Battle Call to Beauty, 1929 (Box 29)
  - Battle Cry of the Mothers, 1915 (Box 29)
  - Be Glad of Ardor (Box 29)
  - Be Lovely (Box 29)
  - Be Rid of Things, 1921 (Box 29)
  - Beakers (Box 29)
  - Beasts of Burden (Box 29)
  - Beautiful Legs, 1934 (Box 29)
  - Beautiful Young Man, 1952 (Box 29)
  - Beauty is for All, 1922 (Box 29)
  - Beauty Specialist, 1933 (Box 29)
  - Beauty, Thy Call Must Wait (Box 29)
  - Becky (Box 29)
  - Behold My Kings, 1921 (Box 29)
  - Behold the Angel (Box 29)
  - Behold the Builders, 1922 (Box 29)
  - Being Up There, 1930 (Box 29)
  - Benediction, 1919 (Box 29)
  - Bird Census, 1939 (Box 29)
  - Bird in the Courtyard (Box 29)
  - Bird Rapture (Box 29)
  - Birthday Cake, 1940 (Box 29)
  - Blood (Box 29)
  - Blue Dusk, 1924 (Box 29)
  - Bond Invisible, 1913 (Box 29)
  - Born Again, 1953 (Box 29)
  - Both Took Place, 1953 (Box 29)
  - Born Perfect, 1938 (Box 29)
  - Bread, 1928 (Box 29)
  - Bread Awaits, 1920 (Box 29)
  - Breakfast Tray, 1921 (Box 29)
  - Bright Flame Burning, 1932 (Box 29)
  - Broken Resolutions (Box 29)
  - Bruised Morning, 1935 (Box 29)
  - Buckwheat Field Under Moon, 1939 (Box 29)
  - Bugle Call to Mothers, 1949 (Box 29)
  - Burning Flake of Gold, 1940 (Box 29)
  - Busy Signal (Box 29)
  - Buttons and Trash, 1922 (Box 29)
  - By Parsifal Johns, 1939 (Box 29)
  - Cabbages (Box 29)
  - Cactus Flower, 1922 (Box 29)
  - California Earthquake, 1952 (Box 29)
  - California Sun, 1941 (Box 29)
  - California Town (Box 29)
  - Call Me Not Civilized, 1929 (Box 29)
  - Call of Autumn (Box 29)
  - Call of the Land (Box 29)
  - Call to Genius, 1921 (Box 29)
  - Cameo, 1922 (Box 29)
  - Camp Fire Song, 1941 (Box 29)
  - Camp Reunion, 1934 (Box 29)
  - Camp Reunion, 1935 (Box 29)
  - Camp Reunion Easter Song, 1939 (Box 29)
  - Can't Afford (Box 29)
  - Carrot, 1941 (Box 29)
  - Cash Register (Box 29)
  - Catching the New Paltz Mail, 1936 (Box 29)
  - Celestial Bombardier (Box 29)
  - Celestial Kiss (Box 29)
  - Celestial Radio, 1935 (Box 29)
  - Celibate, 1927 (Box 29)
  - Challenge from a Star (Box 29)
  - Challenge to Myself, 1937 (Box 29)
  - Challenge to the Magna Charta Dames (Box 29)
  - Challenge to the Soul of Philadelphia, 1929 (Box 29)
  - Challenge to Womankind, 1922 (Box 29)
  - Chance to Love, 1923 (Box 29)
  - Chariot of the Age, 1920 (Box 29)
  - Child of the Hot City (Box 29)
  - Child Who Went Away (Box 29)
  - Choice, 1917 (Box 29)
  - Choirs of Spring, 1922 (Box 29)
  - Choosing, 1920 (Box 29)
  - Christ Speaks to Willie Sutton, 1952 (Box 29)
  - Christian, 1913 (Box 29)
  - Christmas, 1928 (Box 29)
  - Christmas After War, 1920 (Box 29)
  - Christmas Fairy (Box 29)
  - Christmas Miracle, 1912 (Box 29)
  - Christmas Orange, 1924 (Box 29)
  - Christmas Tree of the Angels (Box 29)
  - Church Bell Time in Stratford, 1923 (Box 29)
  - City (Box 29)
  - City, Reply, 1922 (Box 29)
  - City Smoke, 1922 (Box 29)
  - Clearing Day, 1938 (Box 30)
  - Cleaving Power, 1920 (Box 30)
  - Climb Up and See the Stars (Box 30)
  - Clothes, 1922 (Box 30)
  - Clotheslines in November (Box 30)
  - Cloud, 1923 (Box 30)
  - Clowning (Box 30)
  - Clue Look From You (Box 30)
  - Coin of Life, 1922 (Box 30)
  - Color of Winter (Box 30)
  - Colorado Cavaliers (Box 30)
  - Come Along to Cheerfulness, 1924 (Box 30)
  - Come, Daughters All (Box 30)
  - Come You Who Call for Conquerors, 1928 (Box 30)
  - Comfort in the Sky, 1923 (Box 30)
  - Coming Man, 1914 (Box 30)
  - Coming of Day (Box 30)
  - Command (Box 30)
  - Commander, 1919 (Box 30)
  - Commandment, 1919 (Box 30)
  - Common Dust (Box 30)
  - Communion, 1918 (Box 30)
  - Comparisons (Box 30)
  - Comrade, Hail, 1929 (Box 30)
  - Confirmation (Box 30)
  - Conflict, 1923 (Box 30)
  - Congregation of Tress, 1939 (Box 30)
  - Conquerors, 1911 (Box 30)
  - Consolation (Box 30)
  - Conversazione, 1919 (Box 30)
  - Cool as a Bird, 1921 (Box 30)
  - Coronation (Box 30)
  - Coronation Peak (Box 30)
  - Corrigan (Box 30)
  - Cosmic Mother (Box 30)
  - Cosmos Has A Cry (Box 30)
  - Cosy Afternoon, 1922 (Box 30)
  - Cottage in the Mountains (Box 30)
  - Courage (Box 30)
  - Courage for Today, 1923 (Box 30)
  - Creation, 1923 (Box 30)
  - Creator Man, 1929 (Box 30)
  - Crimson Dahlias, 1924 (Box 30)
  - Crown Jewels, 1925 (Box 30)
  - Crowning Day, 1928 (Box 30)
  - Crowning Love (Box 30)
  - Crucify Me (Box 30)
  - Cruelty, 1920 (Box 30)
  - Crusader (Box 30)
  - Cry Against Incumbrance (Box 30)
  - Cry at Sunset, 1913 (Box 30)
  - Cry Eternal, 1922 (Box 30)
  - Cry for Conquest (Box 30)
  - Cry of All Workers (Box 30)
  - Cry of Youth, 1921 (Box 30)
  - Cry to the Heart of a Man (Box 30)
  - Crystal Door Knob (Box 30)
  - Daily Paper (Box 30)
  - Daily Toil, 1929 (Box 30)
  - Dame Nature, 1922 (Box 30)
  - Daughterhood (Box 30)
  - David's Aura, 1952 (Box 30)
  - Dawn, 1925 (Box 30)
  - Dawn is a Thief, 1922 (Box 30)
  - Days (Box 30)
  - Daytime Moon (Box 30)
  - Dear God We Thank Thee in This Hour, 1938 (Box 30)
  - Death Chamber, 1953 (Box 30)
  - Deed, 1919 (Box 30)
  - Deep Delicious, 1933 (Box 30)
  - Deep Dipper, 1940 (Box 30)
  - Deep Places, 1953 (Box 30)
  - Democracy (Box 30)
  - Dentist (Box 30)
  - Deserted (Box 30)
  - Despair is Never Right, 1922 (Box 30)
  - Diamonds Are In Your Crown (Box 30)
  - Difference (Box 30)
  - Diner, 1951 (Box 30)
  - Dinner is Served (Box 30)
  - Disobedience, 1918 (Box 30)
  - Divers Rejoice (Box 30)
  - Divine Foretelling, 1922 (Box 30)
  - Doer, 1919 (Box 30)
  - Doll in the Window (Box 30)
  - Don't Cry for the Moon, 1922 (Box 30)
  - Door (Box 30)
  - Doorstep (Box 30)
  - Doubters (Box 30)
  - Down by Hedge Row, 1922 (Box 30)
  - Dream (Box 30)
  - Drum Beats Out of Heaven, 1937 (Box 30)
  - Dumb Brute, 1922 (Box 30)
  - Dwelling Place (Box 30)
  - Easter is Now (Box 30)
  - Education, 1922 (Box 30)
  - Eggs (Box 30)
  - Eight O'Clock Song (Box 30)
  - Eisenhower's Proposal, 1953 (Box 30)
  - Elevator Man (Box 30)
  - Enchanted Land (Box 30)
  - Enchanted Night, 1923 (Box 30)
  - Encouragement (Box 30)
  - End of the Feast (Box 30)
  - Energy (Box 30)
  - English Clover, 1923 (Box 30)
  - Epicure, 1923 (Box 30)
  - Eternal Hunger (Box 30)
  - Eternal Moment (Box 30)
  - Euclid of Megar (Box 30)
  - Europe, 1924 (Box 30)
  - Even Karma (Box 30)
  - Evening Star, 1933 (Box 30)
  - Everybody's Song, 1922 (Box 30)
  - Everything is Ecstasy (Box 30)
  - Evil Hearted, 1925 (Box 30)
  - Fabulous Grain (Box 30)
  - Face in the Mirror, 1922 (Box 30)
  - Faerie Queen (Box 30)
  - Failure (Box 30)
  - Fairy Kitten at Faeriedel (Box 30)
  - Family Junk (Box 30)
  - Far Ago in Fairyland, 1935 (Box 30)
  - Farm Drudge, 1918 (Box 30)
  - Feather Moon (Box 30)
  - Fields in August, 1926 (Box 30)
  - Fiery Angel (Box 30)
  - Fiery Dreams (Box 30)
  - Finding Peace (Box 30)
  - Fire Divine (Box 30)
  - Fire in Bloom (Box 30)
  - Firelight (Box 30)
  - First Born (Box 30)
  - First Day of Spring, 1952 (Box 30)
  - First Hot Day (Box 30)
  - Flagon, 1952 (Box 30)
  - Flapper Speaks (Box 30)
  - Flavor, 1933 (Box 30)
  - Flesh (Box 30)
  - Flight, 1929 (Box 30)
  - Flood Me With Light (Box 30)
  - Floodlight the Flag (Box 30)
  - Flower, 1937 (Box 30)
  - Flowering Tulip Tree, 1934 (Box 30)
  - Fog, 1923 (Box 30)
  - Folks Say (Box 30)
  - For Father Raymond (Box 30)
  - Ford Hall, 1914 (Box 30)
  - Foreknowledge, 1935 (Box 30)
  - Forest Fire (Box 30)
  - Forward, 1923 (Box 30)
  - Forward, March, 1918 (Box 30)
  - Four Minute Boil (Box 30)
  - Four Morning Stars (Box 30)
  - Fourth Dimension, 1942 (Box 30)
  - Fragrance (Box 30)
  - Framework, 1924 (Box 30)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt (Box 30)
  - Frannie, Flying (Box 30)
  - Freedom is a Godly Word, 1952 (Box 30)
  - Freighters, 1920 (Box 30)
  - Fresh Beginning, 1948 (Box 30)
  - Fresh Born (Box 30)
  - Freshly Fallen Gold, 1942 (Box 30)
  - Fretful Words (Box 30)
  - Friend, O My Friend, 1918 (Box 30)
  - Friendship (Box 30)
  - From a Hill Top, 1923 (Box 30)
  - From Thinking Hard and Thinking Long, 1916 (Box 30)
  - Fruit Picture (Box 30)
  - Frustration (Box 30)
  - Game of Life (Box 31)
  - Games and Beauty (Box 31)
  - Gandhi, 1926 (Box 31)
  - Garbage Pail, 1953 (Box 31)
  - Garden of the Heart, 1920 (Box 31)
  - Gauzy Curtain (Box 31)
  - Gaze Upon Your Body (Box 31)
  - Genius, 1923 (Box 31)
  - George Washington Carver, 1950 (Box 31)
  - Gifts, 1922 (Box 31)
  - Girl in Love (Box 31)
  - Girl Scouts (Box 31)
  - Girl Song, 1952 (Box 31)
  - Girlhood (Box 31)
  - Girls, 1920 (Box 31)
  - Glamour, 1952 (Box 31)
  - Globe Trotter (Box 31)
  - Gloria, 1953 (Box 31)
  - Glorious Young (Box 31)
  - Glory of Tree Tops, 1935 (Box 31)
  - Go to Sleep Song (Box 31)
  - Goal (Box 31)
  - Goals, 1936 (Box 31)
  - God be Merciful, 1930 (Box 31)
  - God Bless the World (Box 31)
  - God Calls the Day (Box 31)
  - God Does Not Weep (Box 31)
  - God Has Abundance (Box 31)
  - God is Not Too Busy, 1926 (Box 31)
  - God Prays (Box 31)
  - God That I Love, 1930 (Box 31)
  - God the Artist (Box 31)
  - God Will Forgive, 1936 (Box 31)
  - God's Dream, 1913 (Box 31)
  - Gods Have Prepared (Box 31)
  - Gods in Our Garden (Box 31)
  - God's Man, 1909 (Box 31)
  - God's Velvet, 1921 (Box 31)
  - God's Whip, 1914 (Box 31)
  - Gold Giver, 1927 (Box 31)
  - Gold On Your Pillow, 1933 (Box 31)
  - Gold Star Mother of Mine, 1934 (Box 31)
  - Golden Day of God, 1923 (Box 31)
  - Golden Hearted Woman, 1924 (Box 31)
  - Good Morning (Box 31)
  - Good Old George and the Slogan (Box 31)
  - Governor's Mother, 1948 (Box 31)
  - Graduation, 1927 (Box 31)
  - Graduation Day Poem, 1928 (Box 31)
  - Grandma Reynolds (Box 31)
  - Gratitude (Box 31)
  - Great Are With Us (Box 31)
  - Great Beyond, 1933 (Box 31)
  - Greater Love, 1917 (Box 31)
  - Greatest Sin, 1930 (Box 31)
  - Greatness, 1922 (Box 31)
  - Green Tree (Box 31)
  - Greetings to Lohali, 1922 (Box 31)
  - Grief (Box 31)
  - Guest to Her Hostess (Box 31)
  - Hail the Americas (Box 31)
  - Hallowed Ground, 1914 (Box 31)
  - Halo Was Always There, 1939 (Box 31)
  - Haloes (Box 31)
  - Hands (Box 31)
  - Harness of Flesh, 1933 (Box 31)
  - Harriet Burch, 1952 (Box 31)
  - Harvest, 1935 (Box 31)
  - Have You the Price (Box 31)
  - Haying Time (Box 31)
  - Hear Me (Box 31)
  - Heart of a Queen, 1924 (Box 31)
  - Heart's Corner (Box 31)
  - Heart's Offering (Box 31)
  - Heat (Box 31)
  - Heaven Drift, 1936 (Box 31)
  - Heaven Is Happening, 1931 (Box 31)
  - Heavenly (Box 31)
  - Her Opera Coat (Box 31)
  - Here is a God (Box 31)
  - Here's to Jean (Box 31)
  - Hidden Treasure, 1924 (Box 31)
  - Higher Genius, 1925 (Box 31)
  - Hilltop Miracle (Box 31)
  - Holocaust, 1926 (Box 31)
  - Holy Word, 1953 (Box 31)
  - Home Longing, 1924 (Box 31)
  - Homespun, 1927 (Box 31)
  - Horses (Box 31)
  - Hour Has Struck, 1914 (Box 31)
  - House With the Crimson Shutters, 1936 (Box 31)
  - Housewife (Box 31)
  - Housewife Waits, 1922 (Box 31)
  - Housewife's Hymn, 1913 (Box 31)
  - How Beautiful (Box 31)
  - How Could I Know (Box 31)
  - How is Philippa to Live, 1914 (Box 31)
  - How Many Prophets (Box 31)
  - How Radiant Is Snow (Box 31)
  - How the End Came, 1920 (Box 31)
  - Human Touch, 1924 (Box 31)
  - Humility, 1922 (Box 31)
  - Hunter (Box 31)
  - Hunter Striker (Box 31)
  - Hymn to Christ (Box 31)
  - Hymn to December (Box 31)
  - Hymn to Democracy, 1919 (Box 31)
  - Hymn to Labor, 1924 (Box 31)
  - Hypocrisy (Box 31)
  - I Am, 1953 (Box 31)
  - I Am A Shining Person (Box 31)
  - I Am Glad of the City (Box 31)
  - I Am Playing A Tune on the Trees, 1938 (Box 31)
  - I Am Sick of the Judgments, 1923 (Box 31)
  - I Came to Sing, 1924 (Box 31)
  - I Choose the Red Pansy, 1921 (Box 31)
  - I Dare Believe (Box 31)
  - I Dream of Coming Artists, 1921 (Box 31)
  - I Follow Love, 1923 (Box 31)
  - I Got a Whiff of Spring, 1923 (Box 31)
  - I Greet My Higher Self (Box 31)
  - I Have a Question to Ask of Men, 1919 (Box 31)
  - I Have Drunk Deep, 1939 (Box 31)
  - I Have Meat, 1918 (Box 31)
  - I Have Not Ceased to Wonder, 1934 (Box 31)
  - I Kept My Tryst With Summer (Box 31)
  - I Like to Do Embroidery, 1923 (Box 31)
  - I Love What I Am (Box 31)
  - I Love Whiteness, 1929 (Box 31)
  - I Need No Incense, 1936 (Box 31)
  - I Saw An Azure Lily, 1923 (Box 31)
  - I Saw My Mother in My Sleep, 1929 (Box 31)
  - I See the Silver, 1935 (Box 31)
  - I Seem to Have Wasted the Morning (Box 31)
  - I Should Like to See a Law (Box 31)
  - I Speak New Patterns, 1941 (Box 31)
  - I Speak to You (Box 31)
  - I Stamp My Radiant Foot, 1939 (Box 31)
  - I Talked With Peary, 1935 (Box 31)
  - I Want to Go Back (Box 31)
  - I Was Built for Glamour, 1953 (Box 31)
  - I Went Forth Gladly (Box 31)
  - I Will Cast My Lot (Box 31)
  - I Will Rise, 1918 (Box 31)
  - Ice Man (Box 31)
  - Ice Storm in the Woods, 1916 (Box 31)
  - I'd Like to be a Jockey (Box 31)
  - Idealist (Box 31)
  - If God Should Come (Box 31)
  - If He Could Speak, 1931 (Box 31)
  - If I Could Rise Some Morning (Box 31)
  - If Some Sweet Space (Box 31)
  - If Thou Had'st Faith (Box 31)
  - If You Saw (Box 31)
  - Illusion, 1918 (Box 31)
  - Immanence, 1922 (Box 31)
  - In a Studio, 1914 (Box 31)
  - In Exchange for a Soul, 1919 (Box 31)
  - In Memory of Theodore Thomas (Box 31)
  - In Modern Language (Box 31)
  - In Spite of War, 1917 (Box 31)
  - In Such An Age (Box 31)
  - In the Beauty Parlor (Box 31)
  - In the Beginning, 1914 (Box 31)
  - In the Garden of People, 1922 (Box 31)
  - In the Laboratory of My Hands (Box 31)
  - In the Night Watches (Box 31)
  - In the Woods (Box 31)
  - Inarticulate, 1922 (Box 31)
  - Incredible, 1928 (Box 31)
  - Indifference, 1920 (Box 31)
  - Ineffectual Angel, 1924 (Box 31)
  - Infant Man (Box 31)
  - Inferno (Box 31)
  - Innermost, 1915 (Box 31)
  - Interfering With the Dream of Spiders, 1939 (Box 32)
  - International Hymn, 1933 (Box 32)
  - Inventor, 1939 (Box 32)
  - Irene Harrison (Box 32)
  - Irritation, 1937 (Box 32)
  - Is It God, 1920 (Box 32)
  - Island (Box 32)
  - It Is - It Is Not You (Box 32)
  - It Is My Glory, 1917 (Box 32)
  - It Is No Longer Enough (Box 32)
  - It Isn't God's Fault, 1932 (Box 32)
  - It Isn't Wine Sauce, 1952 (Box 32)
  - It Was Always People, 1922 (Box 32)
  - I've Fallen In Love (Box 32)
  - Jean Frame (Box 32)
  - Jewel Dusk (Box 32)
  - Jewels (Box 32)
  - John Haynes Holmes, 1929 (Box 32)
  - John Pollard of Virginia (Box 32)
  - John the Baptist (Box 32)
  - John's Grill, 1952 (Box 32)
  - Johnny's Railway Journey (Box 32)
  - Jolly Song of Noise, 1939 (Box 32)
  - Journey By Bus (Box 32)
  - Journeys (Box 32)
  - Joy of Life, 1923 (Box 32)
  - Joy of Shopping (Box 32)
  - Judge Me Not, 1921 (Box 32)
  - Judgment, 1918 (Box 32)
  - Judgments, 1916 (Box 32)
  - July Dawn, 1922 (Box 32)
  - June Rapture, 1910 (Box 32)
  - Just a Ditty, 1924 (Box 32)
  - Just a Sketch of Emily V. Hammond (Box 32)
  - Just As They Are (Box 32)
  - Just at the Point (Box 32)
  - Just Before Dawn (Box 32)
  - Kagawa (Box 32)
  - Keep Off, 1923 (Box 32)
  - Keys (Box 32)
  - Killing's On (Box 32)
  - King, 1913 (Box 32)
  - King Abdicates (Box 32)
  - King Is Dead, 1952 (Box 32)
  - Kinship, 1915 (Box 32)
  - Kitten At Faeriedel (Box 32)
  - Kitten With the Earnest Look, 1939 (Box 32)
  - Knightly Plumage, 1939 (Box 32)
  - Know Thyself, 1911 (Box 32)
  - Korea, 1952 (Box 32)
  - Krishnamurti, 1928 (Box 32)
  - Ladder (Box 32)
  - Lady At A Loss (Box 32)
  - Lady Betty Gives Away Her Flowers, 1923 (Box 32)
  - Lady of Dreams, 1927 (Box 32)
  - Language, 1929 (Box 32)
  - Larks and Lambs (Box 32)
  - Larkspur Mood (Box 32)
  - Late Corn Fields, 1922 (Box 32)
  - Law, 1923 (Box 32)
  - Law of the Sea, 1913 (Box 32)
  - Laziness, 1922 (Box 32)
  - Leader (Box 32)
  - Leadership (Box 32)
  - Leaf in the Meadow (Box 32)
  - Leap Year Comes at Last (Box 32)
  - Let Loose the Splendor, 1953 (Box 32)
  - Let the Hear Speak (Box 32)
  - Let There Be Lilies, 1953 (Box 32)
  - Let There Be Loveliness (Box 32)
  - Let Us Declare (Box 32)
  - Let Us Have Faith, 1930 (Box 32)
  - Let Us Rejoice, 1929 (Box 32)
  - Let's Be a Humming Bird (Box 32)
  - Letter to the President, 1944 (Box 32)
  - Lettuce (Box 32)
  - Libation (Box 32)
  - Libel, 1914 (Box 32)
  - Life is As A Moving Picture, 1922 (Box 32)
  - Life Is Not Law, 1942 (Box 32)
  - Life Marches Through Us, 1929 (Box 32)
  - Life the Healer, 1922 (Box 32)
  - Life Weans Her Children (Box 32)
  - Light Ahead, 1922 (Box 32)
  - Light in the Tombs (Box 32)
  - Lightning Rod (Box 32)
  - Lilacs, 1938 (Box 32)
  - Lily in the Sky (Box 32)
  - Limitation, 1925 (Box 32)
  - Lindbergh, 1927 (Box 32)
  - Linen Harvest, 1929 (Box 32)
  - Listen, 1920 (Box 32)
  - Listen In, 1923 (Box 32)
  - Little Friendly Fence, 1937 (Box 32)
  - Little Gardens Under Moonlight, 1926 (Box 32)
  - Little Song of Silence, 1929 (Box 32)
  - Living Canvas (Box 32)
  - Log Cabin, 1934 (Box 32)
  - Logic (Box 32)
  - London After Fog, 1925 (Box 32)
  - Look, 1916 (Box 32)
  - Look at this Mountain, 1939 (Box 32)
  - Lordly Spaces (Box 32)
  - Lost and Found (Box 32)
  - Lost Box, 1939 (Box 32)
  - Lost Love (Box 32)
  - Love, 1920 (Box 32)
  - Love, 1924 (Box 32)
  - Love, 1952 (Box 32)
  - Love Defiant, 1930 (Box 32)
  - Love in Chains (Box 32)
  - Love in Spring, 1920 (Box 32)
  - Love is the Dawn Word (Box 32)
  - Love or Ambition, 1923 (Box 32)
  - Love Song (Box 32)
  - Love Song in War Time, 1918 (Box 32)
  - Love Song of the New Age, 1929 (Box 32)
  - Love That Has Passed (Box 32)
  - Love the Magician, 1920 (Box 32)
  - Love Transcendent (Box 32)
  - Love Universal, 1922 (Box 32)
  - Love Victorious, 1920 (Box 32)
  - Lovely Woman, 1923 (Box 32)
  - Lover Sings of Lilies (Box 32)
  - Lovers, 1928 (Box 32)
  - Lovers By the Hudson (Box 32)
  - Lover's Moon, 1921 (Box 32)
  - Love's Bestowal, 1920 (Box 32)
  - Loves Have There Been, 1922 (Box 32)
  - Love's Passing (Box 32)
  - Love's Resurrection, 1922 (Box 32)
  - Love's Telepathy, 1914 (Box 32)
  - Luminous Heart, 1922 (Box 32)
  - Lungs of the City (Box 32)
  - Luxury (Box 32)
  - Madonna of the Chair (Box 32)
  - Magic, 1950 (Box 32)
  - Maidens of Europe Speak, 1916, 3 folders (Box 32)
  - Majesty, 1923 (Box 32)
  - Make Me Thy Target, God (Box 32)
  - Make of Man the Statue, 1917 (Box 32)
  - Makers of Destiny, 1926 (Box 32)
  - Malady, 1927 (Box 32)
  - Man Challenges Life, 1926 (Box 32)
  - Man in the Mountains (Box 32)
  - Man of Courage, 1929 (Box 32)
  - Man Remembers (Box 32)
  - Man the Deliverer (Box 32)
  - Man the Sculptor, 1922 (Box 33)
  - Man to a Woman, 1922 (Box 33)
  - Man Triumphant (Box 33)
  - Manhattan at Times Square (Box 33)
  - Many Loves, 1929 (Box 33)
  - Marietta, 1942 (Box 33)
  - Marigold Night, 1922 (Box 33)
  - Mark Twain, 1935 (Box 33)
  - Marriage, 1917 (Box 33)
  - Mars Above the Church Towers (Box 33)
  - Martha (Box 33)
  - Masks Off, 1923 (Box 33)
  - Mastery, 1922 (Box 33)
  - Mated (Box 33)
  - May Ella (Box 33)
  - May-Time in London, 1924 (Box 33)
  - May-Time Vision, 1930 (Box 33)
  - Meadows and Birds, 1936 (Box 33)
  - Meaning of the Age, 1921 (Box 33)
  - Meditation (Box 33)
  - Melody, 1919 (Box 33)
  - Memories, 1922 (Box 33)
  - Men From Their Tower, 1948 (Box 33)
  - Merry Go Round (Box 33)
  - Merry Little Brother (Box 33)
  - Messenger (Box 33)
  - Messengers, 1926 (Box 33)
  - Mighty Delinquent, 1951 (Box 33)
  - Mi-La-Raspa Meditates (Box 33)
  - Milady Goes Shopping, 1923 (Box 33)
  - Milk White Butterfly, 1921 (Box 33)
  - Miners, 1926 (Box 33)
  - Minstrels, 1919 (Box 33)
  - Miracle (Box 33)
  - Miracle of Fire (Box 33)
  - Miracle of Lighting, 1939 (Box 33)
  - Miracle of Lovers (Box 33)
  - Miracle of Miracles (Box 33)
  - Miracle of Rain, 1936 (Box 33)
  - Mirror (Box 33)
  - Miss Austin's Table (Box 33)
  - Money, 1922 (Box 33)
  - Moods (Box 33)
  - Moon, A Red Sickle, 1922 (Box 33)
  - Moon Song, 1909 (Box 33)
  - More Joyous Yet, 1939 (Box 33)
  - Morning Glory (Box 33)
  - Morning, Noon and Night (Box 33)
  - Morning Song, 1922 (Box 33)
  - Moth In the Ink Bottle (Box 33)
  - Mother, I Know You're Listening In, 1940 (Box 33)
  - Mother Lean Against Your Wings, 1929 (Box 33)
  - Motherhood, 1953 (Box 33)
  - Motherhood Triumphant, 1920 (Box 33)
  - Mothers and Daughters, 1930 (Box 33)
  - Mother's Thanksgiving (Box 33)
  - Mothers With Little Sons, 1926 (Box 33)
  - Mount Everest, 1953 (Box 33)
  - Mountains Give Freely of Their Beauty, 1937 (Box 33)
  - Mounted Police (Box 33)
  - Moving Day (Box 33)
  - Must She Pay With Her Life, 1913 (Box 33)
  - Must We (Box 33)
  - Mustard Seed (Box 33)
  - My Being Is Eternal, 1951 (Box 33)
  - My Brother's Keeper (Box 33)
  - My Friend's Likeness, 1929 (Box 33)
  - My Heart A Chalice Is This Day (Box 33)
  - My Heart's Haven (Box 33)
  - My Home to Me Is Hallowed Ground (Box 33)
  - My Love for You (Box 33)
  - My Lucky Day (Box 33)
  - My Task is Yoga (Box 33)
  - Names, 1925 (Box 33)
  - Nancy Fullerwood, 1947 (Box 33)
  - Never By Wars, 1918 (Box 33)
  - New Array, 1931 (Box 33)
  - New Birth, 1928 (Box 33)
  - New Command, 1922 (Box 33)
  - New England Landscape in Spring, 1938 (Box 33)
  - New Fern (Box 33)
  - New Galahad (Box 33)
  - New Gospel, 1920 (Box 33)
  - New Paltz Morning, 1935 (Box 33)
  - New Paltz Nights, 1935 (Box 33)
  - New St. Paul's, 1924 (Box 33)
  - New Song, 1938 (Box 33)
  - New Song of Motherhood (Box 33)
  - New Year Dawns (Box 33)
  - New York, 1938 (Box 33)
  - Newly Planted Fields at Night, 1922 (Box 33)
  - Next Morning (Box 33)
  - Night Omnibus, 1935 (Box 33)
  - Night Watchman, 1923 (Box 33)
  - No One to Meet Him, 1920 (Box 33)
  - Noah Said (Box 33)
  - Noble Fellowship, 1926 (Box 33)
  - Noblewoman (Box 33)
  - Noonday Kiss (Box 33)
  - "Not Afraid" Song (Box 33)
  - Not Till Then, 1920 (Box 33)
  - November Morn, 1922 (Box 33)
  - Now Burns October (Box 33)
  - Now I Know (Box 33)
  - Now That the Posts Have Spoken, 1928 (Box 33)
  - Now While The Sun Is So Lovely (Box 33)
  - O Bush of Flame (Box 33)
  - O Friend of Mine (Box 33)
  - O Golden Son of God (Box 33)
  - O Little Window, 1917 (Box 33)
  - O Mind That Knows, 1939 (Box 33)
  - O Women, Tell Me (Box 33)
  - Obeying Orders (Box 33)
  - Ocean, 1918 (Box 33)
  - Ocean Floor, 1937 (Box 33)
  - October (Box 33)
  - October Trees (Box 33)
  - Odin, God of Courage (Box 33)
  - Odin, I would Ask of You, 1930 (Box 33)
  - Ogontz Camp, 1928 (Box 33)